A Guide to the Virginia Auditor of Public Accounts - Expenses of Quarantine Warrants, 1793-1806, 1818
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
Virginia Auditor of Public Accounts - Expenses of Quarantine Warrants, 1793-1806, 1818
The Library of Virginia
APA 141
.45 cu. ft. (1 box)
Virginia Auditor of Public Accounts
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Accession 13211 was transferred from the Auditor of Public Accounts 26 September 1915.
Biographical Information
On 26 December 1792 the General Assembly passed an act prescribing quarantine for ships believed to carry infectious diseases. The auditor issued warrants to pay the expenses of officials supervising the quarantine and for conveying the Governors proclamation to port towns. In 1793 the General Assembly expanded the provisions of the quarantine law to those who entered the state by land as well.
Scope and Content
Warrants, 1793-1806, 1818, paying officials supervising quarantines. Includes payments to the hiring of boats to lookout for fever from the West Indies, guards on vessels, payments for food, gun powder, and alcohol for guards on vessels, payments to doctors, hiring of vessels to act as hospitals for quarantined persons, building of coffins, printing of handbills concerning the quarantine laws, and salaries for superintendents of quarantine. Some documents are signed by James Wood and John Page.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged chronologically.
Contents List
- 1793 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- 1794 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- 1795 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- 1796 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- 1797 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- 1798 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- 1799 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- 1800 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- 1801 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- 1802 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- 1803 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- 1804 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- 1805 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- 1806 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- 1818 (Box 1, Folder 15)